#### **Robert Starbuck**

Web Developer Born 1983

Bristol, BS5 robstarbuck@gmail.com

Fullstack developer striving to keep things simple. My passion at the moment is Go though my career has been spent writing JS. Given my background in design, I have a good eye for what works on a site. I'd fit in best with a small team. I'm experienced with React, Apollo GraphQL, Typescript, JS, CSS, Go, UI Development and Graphics Suites.

# **Experience**

#### **Polecat - Reputation Management**

Frontend Developer April 2017 - Present, Bristol

UI development with React in Typescript, incorporating functional programming with RamdaJS, occasionally contributing as a graphic designer. My contributions were various, and included visualisations with D3 and helping to refactor our sites to use React. The team was very gifted and I learnt a great deal. We strived to a fault for best practices and would always make time for stand-ups, retros and hackathons.

## **Buddi - GPS Solutions**

Ul Developer Oct 2015 - Aug 2016, London

Full stack role building UIs and a new company website with Angular, Shopify and a Sagepay. The site was originally written in Jekyll and later rewritten in Hugo.

## web.cv - Personal Start-up

Founder / Fullstack Sep 2014 - Sep 2015, London

Unsuccessful start-up venture with a team of one. I built the frontend of web.cv with AngularJS with the hope of partnering with a backend engineer. Working by myself was good for discipline, though I certainly lacked the feedback I needed to either move the project forward or understand when to stop.

#### **Merchant Cantos - Marketing Agency**

Fullstack Developer Feb 2014 - Jun 2014, London

Contract work as a front-end dev. Clients included several big names from ebay to facebook. Deadlines were tight and I was hardworked but fully enjoyed my time with the team.

## Y.CO - The Yacht Company

Fullstack Nov 2010 - Aug 2013, Monaco

In-house developer for a yacht company based in Monaco. My role within the company was diverse. I mostly worked autonomously, managing projects and building tools for charter destinations and another for charter yacht selections. Whilst at the company I learnt to speak French. Voilà.

### **Acquire Services - Procurement**

Ul Developer Aug 2007 - Oct 2010, Skipton

Fullstack role using Macromedia Coldfusion. I learnt fast in this role, picking up jQuery and MySql early on. The work involved navigating some truly labyrinthine code to fix bugs and improve performance. Despite having never used a query language I left as someone who could be trusted to write or refactor a complex query.

### **Sky Sports**

ActionScript Developer June 2006 - Aug 2007, Harrogate

Work placement aiming learn Flash ActionScript, surely the shape of things to come!. It wasn't long until I moved onto JavaScript as well. The department was always busy and I helped out on a number published projects.

## **Education**

BA in Electronic Media Design 2001 - 2004, University of Sunderland BTEC Design & A level Photography 1999 - 2001, Harrogate Art College 9 GCSEs (Maths, English) 1994 - 1999, Harrogate Grammar School